ADAM BATY

PROFILE

Software Engineer with over 2 years of hands-on experience in software development, devops, and cloud infrastructure. Specializing in web development using C# with the ASP.NET Razor framework, and Python with the Flask framework. Motivated learner who looks at new challenges as an opportunity for growth.

SKILLS

Python Flask Azure DevOps
C# ASP.NET Razor Git
Terraform CI/CD Google Cloud Platform

EXPERIENCE

Huntington National Bank | Columbus, OH

Software Engineer

JANUARY 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2022

- Web development for the customer-facing web application using C#/ASP.NET Razor
- Configured CI/CD pipelines in Azure DevOps with YAML
- Developed in Terraform to build out infrastructure automation in Google Cloud Platform

Cooper Tire and Rubber Company | Findlay, OH

Software Development Co-Op

AUGUST 2020 - JANUARY 2021

- Developed a web page for administrators to easily access telemetry data from scratch developed in Python's Flask framework
- Worked with 2 mentors to learn while developing applications
- Tech stack was primarily, Python, Flask, SQL (SQL Server)

Bowling Green State University | Bowling Green, OH

Classroom Technician - Information Technology Services

MAY 2017 - AUGUST 2020

- Maintained and repaired audio/visual equipment in the classrooms
- Provided quality customer service and training to instructors
- Scheduled tasks, lead, and motivated student employees

EDUCATION

Bowling Green State University | Bowling Green, OH

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science - Business Systems
DECEMBER 2020